I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Ryusuke. I'm going to form
the ultimate band.
So will I.
Umm...
I was hoping to borrow that
Dying Breed CD from their indie days.
Koyuki. If you have time, follow me.
Ryusuke-kun, how's the guitar?
-Concentrate on the sound.
-Sound?
Close your eyes and focus on the sound.
Can you hear the bass?
The level is different.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I'm about to go there.
Well, don't get pissed.
Okay, I'll be there.
Ryusuke-kun, is something wrong?
Yeah, something came up.
He was awfully mad.
Didn't you hear me? I said no thanks.
I told you I'm just waiting for my brother,
not for fuckin' guys like you.
I'm not a whore like you think!
No, I didn't mean it! Sorry.
Bullshit, you fuckin' bastard! Go away!
Wow...You're too scary.
Scary?! Who do you think makes me scary?
Hey, what's going on? Who are they?
Well, they were hitting on me.
They should go to hell.
They're both freaked out like shit.
'Cuz you're late!
Well, sorry about that.
Oh, yeah. Let me introduce you.
Koyuki is 14, same as you, Maho.
I know!
-And what'll you have?
-Whatever.
Okay, then. Koyuki, take care of it.
I'm going to talk to Taira, the bassist.
I've gotta catch him early,
or he'll be taken.
The main thing in a band is...
a bassist and drummer.
Is a beef bowl okay?
Okay, see you later.
I called some friends from school.
You don't mind, do you?
Sure.
Say, the other day, I met this guy,
and he tried to pick me up!
But he was such an asshole!
But he had a BMW convertible!
Really? That's cool! I love that car!
I know...But he was awfully creepy!
His eyes twitched in this weird way
and it made me sick!
But Risa, you always
get stuck with weirdos.
I know...
Why don't you wait for Maho's rejects?
Oh no. Some poor-looking foreigners
hit on me earlier.
-Poor foreigners? That sucks!
-Yeah...
There's never cool guys.
I like guys riding Porsches.
-Then I want a Ferrari.
-Me too!
Hey, let's go clubbing now.
We might find our dream guy.
Yay, let's go!
Yeah, I wanna go, but I'm broke.
-Umm...I...
-Come on!
Fine, the dream guy will pay for you.
Yeah, free buy!
I have something to
take care of, so I'll be going.
They don't teach English properly
in Japan, is what I feel.
Dutch, huh?
Your Japanese has improved.
Is that meant to be a compliment?
Eiji and I jammed the other day.
He's getting better, amazingly fast.
I finish school this year,
and I'm thinking seriously about my future.
If you want to make music with me,
bring me a really great vocalist.
A vocalist, huh?
Yo!
W-what happened?
I have no place to crash tonight.
So I'm going to Ryusuke's place.
Umm, the other day...
I'm sorry I laughed at you
about not knowing kanji.
Don't worry about it.
Besides, I am bad at kanji.
I got fired from a diner yesterday
because I didn't know the language.
Are you serious?
I was so mad, I yelled and cried
that I was going back to America.
Then my dad slapped me.
Are you all right?
You're very kind, Koyuki.
But you don't seem to like my friends.
B-because I left early?
You didn't try to talk to them.
-But the language...
-ls that it? The language?
Everyone says the same thing.
Well, let's go see Beck!
Huh? Beck?!
Beck!
Hey, Beck! I haven't seen you
in a while, yet you ignore me!
Please help me, Maho-chan!
Stop adding "-chan" to my name.
Hi, Beck...
How's it going?
Brother taking care of you?
Such a pretty full moon.
It's a full moon tonight.
Full moon sways...
Gently in the night of one fine day...
Maho, you're amazing. You can
speak English and you sing great.
And you're cute...
I know you'll make it as a singer!
As if!
I have no talent as a singer.
My dream is to study movies in New York.
Full moon sways...
Gently in the night of one fine day.
On my way...
Looking for a moment with my dear...
It's my favorite song by Dying Breed.
Hey, Tanaka!
Find something?
Oh, it's you, Izumi-chan!
Don't scare me like that!
-So, are you willing?
-Huh?
Stop by the municipal pool at 6 pm.
Pool?
Don't be late, now.
You'll find out when you get there.
The municipal pool?
Well then, I'll see you later.
"Business envelopes, fabric tape,
aluminum foil, polyester bags"
Please consider the financing!
Please! Thank you!
"Saito Paper Company"
5:30 huh?
There!
And now...
Hey, kid...
Please don't grab onto the lane ropes.
I know, but...
Hey, kid! If you're in the
50 meter pool, don't stop!
-There he is.
-Let's go home.
Hey, your kick is okay,
but you pull with your elbow,
so you're not cutting into the water.
Huh? Oh...
Okay! Hook your feet
against the pool and practice!
-Let's give it a try!
-W-who is he?
He's the famous man of this pool.
Famous?
His name's Saito-san, and he
was once an Olympic swimmer.
So whenever he sees a poor swimmer,
he can't help but teach.
An Olympic swimmer?
Well, he's not a bad guy.
Huh? That's strange...
Izumi!
He's in the 25-meter pool.
One, two, three, four...
Just as I figured!
Koyuki got caught!
Kid, are you ready?
You're giving me a
15-meter handicap, right?
Yeah...This is serious, a real contest.
Yes. And if I win?
As promised, I'll train you man to man.
All right.
-And if you lose...
-lf I lose?
I'll hit you!
Huh?!
And I won't hold back!
Why would you do that?!
Kid...In the grown-up world,
there are many painful things!
Now get set!
Ready!
Go!
Five meters.
Ten meters.
Fifteen meters!
Victory is mine!
I...did it!
Saito-san...
It's been a long time.
Izumi-chan!
Oh!
You're in the swim club at my alma mater,
Ihara East Middle School!
How is Suzuki-sensei's lumbago?
I think it's much better.
Saito-san, please come
and coach us again!
Oh, really? I'm glad that
someone like you appreciates me!
-Then you talked to him?
-Yeah.
You're really...
I asked him for some advice. And then...
And then?
We somehow wound up in a race.
Koyuki-kun!
Want some?
-N-no, thank you.
-No?
Well, let's practice again tomorrow!
Good night!
He's like a different person.
Saito-san is a really warm-hearted
gentleman outside the pool.
He listens to U.K. Rock bands, I think.
U.K.?
English rock bands.
Like the Beatles and stuff.
The Stones are British, too, right?
Yes, the Zeppelin too.
I feel like I'm in the way.
Huh?
I have an early curfew. Good night!
-Is swimming fun?
-Yeah.
-Think you'll continue?
Really? I'm glad.
I was going to stop by
Ryusuke-kun's place.
Maybe I'll join you.
You have a game on Sunday?
Yeah, Mit-chan asked me.
Umm...your grip...
-He just needed a player...
-Ryusuke-kun, your grip...
Huh? You say something, Koyuki?
Koyuki has a present for you, Ryusuke-kun.
A present?
An unleashed dog may be taken away.
I have been worried
how he doesn't come home lately...
Wait a minute.
Damn, it's dusty.
You can have this.
No way!
You've been listening
to a lot of music lately.
I figured you might want to play, too.
It looks quite old.
It's not much, but the sound is good.
Wow!
There we go.
-A string broke.
-What song was that?
-I just played whatever.
-It's the blues, right?
Yeah.
I love the way you play, Ryusuke-kun.
I'm gonna play every waking moment
and get better and better!
Huh? Yeah.
Oh, Ryusuke-kun!
Mit-chan is steaming mad!
-Wasn't it at 4:30?
-No, 3:00!
It's already the last inning!
I heard 4:30.
Who's that pitcher?
The vocalist for The Crowd,
Manabu Miyazawa.
Is he famous?
The Crowd had a huge following
and people thought it was
a matter of time before they debuted.
But the drummer suddenly quit
and the band broke up.
The end was really pitiful.
-Hey! Where're you throwing?!
-Oops! That's weird!
I can't hit the bat!
Batter! Don't move too much!
-Strike!
-He doesn't seem so great...
If he joins my band,
Taira-kun will join, too.
Ryusuke-kun...Look at the other bench.
Eiji...
He's been asking Manabu-kun
to join since the Serial Mama stuff.
Hey, Ryusuke!
-Do you know what time it is?!
-Sorry, I had the wrong time.
I told you we had just enough players.
Sorry.
'Cuz of you, I had to call the
one person in the world I didn't wanna.
Not...Chiba?
Ryusuke-kun?
-I owe him 30,000 yen.
-Hey! Where's my money?!
"Pay when you can."
Don't they have that in Japan?
Shut up! You ingrate!
Chiba! We only have the field
'til 5:00! Hurry it up!
Just you wait, Ryusuke.
Awright!
Ball!
Frankly, I don't care for Manabu's vocals.
But in order to get Taira-kun,
I have no choice.
-Then what about Chiba?
-Huh? I've never heard him sing.
Chiba has charisma. He has
more aura than Manabu-kun.
Oww!
You should've moved!
Dammit! I'll kill you!
Oh, c'mon, don't get so uptight.
You're the losers anyway.
Calm down.
Don't touch me!
Oh well...
Stop...
Stop!
Koyuki...
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
I like Kasumi-chan of the tobacco shop.
"Next Episode"
But I also like Ranko-chan
of the family restaurant.
"Next Episode"